A Finding Aid to the Blanche Lazzell Papers, 1893-1956, bulk 1901-1940, in the Archives of American Art AAA.lazzblan
Archives of American Art
- Photographic Material, 1897-1956; Series 8; 0.5 Linear feet Boxes 5-6
  - Group Photos of "Gallery 200" Artists at Provincetown, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Assorted Kodak Films Envelopes, 1923-1951 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Color Slides of Provincetown Studio, 1942-1950 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Color Slides of Artwork, circa 1940 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Lantern Slide of Red and White Petunia, circa 1940 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Artifacts, circa 1910-1956; Series 9; 0.1 Linear feet Box 6
  Artifacts include 2 metal signs and 1 paint palette in a metal case.
  The signs are first, followed by the paint palette.
  - "Franklin Wheeling" Metal Sign, circa 1910-1956 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - "Insured Peabody Wheeling" Metal Sign, circa 1910-1956 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Paint Palette in Metal Case, circa 1910-1956 (Box 6, Folder 5)